Guide to the Pach Brothers Portrait Photograph Collection 1867-1947, undated (bulk 1880s-1940s) PR 84
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Oversize and Group Portraits
  - Subseries I: Individuals and Family Groups
    - Childs, George W. and family, 1870 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 74)
    - Edison, Thomas Alva, 1909 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 74)
    - Grant, General Fred, and General Leonard Wood and wives, 1909 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 74)
    - Hayes, Rutherford B., and his cabinet (copy of print), undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 75)
    - Lincoln, Abraham (copy of print), undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 75)
    - McKinley, William, and his cabinet, 1901 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 75)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, As a Roughrider, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 76)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, At Montauk Point, New York, 1898 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 76)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, Trophy room at Sycamore Hill, Oyster Bay, NY, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 76)
  - Subseries II: Corporate Groups
    - Delta Upsilon Fraternity founders (2), 1883, 1908 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 77)
    - F. W. Woolworth and Associates, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 77)
    - New York Giants baseball team, 1908 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 77)
    - New York Supreme Court Justices, Appellate Division, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 78)
    - Public Service Commission, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 78)
    - S. H. Kress and company, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 79)
    - Singer Sewing Machine Company Directors, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 79)
    - Theatrical Committee of the Allied Ball, 1917 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 79)
    - Vail, Theodore Newton, and group receiving the first transatlantic telephone message, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 79)
    - W. & J. Sloan and Company, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 79)
- Series III: Buildings
  Series III. Buildings holds photographs of street scenes that include portraits of buildings where the Pach Brothers had their studios in New Jersey and New York City; a glimpse of one of their office interiors can be seen in the brothers' group portrait in Box 6, Folder 50. This series also holds one photograph of Madison Square Garden and one of the Fifth Avenue Hotel, both in New York.
  - Fifth Avenue Hotel, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 80)
  - Madison Square Garden, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 80)
  - Pach Brothers studio, Long Branch, NJ (2), 1867 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 80)
  - G.W. Pach Photographer Wagon, Long Branch, NJ, 1867 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 80)
  - Pach Brothers studio, 858 Broadway, New York, NY, [1873] (Offsite-box 9, Folder 80)
  - Pach Brothers studio, 841 Broadway, New York, NY, [1878] (Offsite-box 9, Folder 80)
  - Pach Brothers studio, 935 Broadway, New York, NY, [1895] (Offsite-box 9, Folder 80)
  - Pach Brothers studio, 935 Broadway, New York, NY, 1905 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 80)